{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3203","name":"Happy's Pizza #11","address":"6412 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207","owner":"Tammy Berry","licenseNumber":"057460","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.00842,42.34386","geojson":{"id":"3203","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.008415933,42.3438576720001]},"properties":{"name":"Happy's Pizza #11","owner":"Tammy Berry","address":"6412 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"057460","establishmentid":"3203","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/29/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622615","name":"Le Petit Dejeuner","address":"6470 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"5108","name":"Riverwalk Cafe Mt. Elliott","address":"120 Mt Elliott Rd","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"5317","name":"Comfort Cafe","address":"6533 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"2764","name":"Little Caesar's Pizza #164","address":"500 Mt Elliott St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1800","name":"Wendy's","address":"6601 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"651","name":"Harbortown Pizza & Subs Inc. d/b/a Jet's","address":"3420 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"5161","name":"Southern Fire Bistro & Lounge","address":"575 Bellevue St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1882","name":"City Pekin Chinese Food","address":"6905 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1188","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #345","address":"6931 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"503","name":"Peking Express","address":"3444 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"45617","inspectionDate":"2019-03-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Food","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On top of the Cooler (3  door)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-03-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Digital Thermometer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-04-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-03-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-203.11","violationDescription":"(A)  A HANDWASHING SINK or an approved automatic handwashing unit shall be provided as necessary for their convenient use by EMPLOYEES in areas specified and not fewer than the number of HANDWASHING SINKS required by LAW shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n(B)  If APPROVED, when FOOD exposure is limited and HANDWASHING SINKS are not conveniently available, such as in some mobile or TEMPORARY FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS or at some VENDING MACHINE LOCATIONS, EMPLOYEES may use chemically treated towelettes for handwashing.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing lavatories","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Inadequate","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-03-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"doors","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-04-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \r\n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\r\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\r\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\r\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"wet","problemDescription":"Stored on","subProblem":"Counter","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Sanitizer bucket","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-202.18","violationDescription":"Filters or other grease extracting EQUIPMENT shall be designed to be readily removable for cleaning and replacement if not designed to be cleaned in place.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation hood filter(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing FILTERS","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-04-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Unnecessary item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"UTILITY ROOM","subLocation":"Around the Mop sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41655","inspectionDate":"2018-03-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"Through out the day as necessary","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Missing Covered waste container","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"On the floor Single Use Items","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\r\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\r\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\r\n         (2)     The container; and\r\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Smoking","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Mop sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Smoke only in designated areas as restricted above."}]},{"inspectionid":"40556","inspectionDate":"2017-10-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"38039","inspectionDate":"2017-02-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-203.11","violationDescription":"(A)  A HANDWASHING SINK or an approved automatic handwashing unit shall be provided as necessary for their convenient use by EMPLOYEES in areas specified and not fewer than the number of HANDWASHING SINKS required by LAW shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n(B)  If APPROVED, when FOOD exposure is limited and HANDWASHING SINKS are not conveniently available, such as in some mobile or TEMPORARY FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS or at some VENDING MACHINE LOCATIONS, EMPLOYEES may use chemically treated towelettes for handwashing.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing lavatories","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Inadequate","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Test strips","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"No Paper toweling","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-501.110","violationDescription":"(A) Dressing rooms shall be used by EMPLOYEES if the EMPLOYEES regularly change their clothes in the establishment.\r\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be used for the orderly storage of EMPLOYEE clothing and other possessions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/designated storage area(s)","subItem":"for employee belongings storage","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Outerwear","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"In prep area","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (pizza-prep)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-202.18","violationDescription":"Filters or other grease extracting EQUIPMENT shall be designed to be readily removable for cleaning and replacement if not designed to be cleaned in place.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation hood filter(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not readily removable","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the FILTERS","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Replace to be readily removable."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"walls","problemDescription":"Greasy","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"To the left of Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"Under the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Behind the Pizza oven","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-04-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3203"}}